Guide to the Army Specialized Training Division, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, circa 1940-1963; Accession 19ND-A-170
  - Staff Officers School
    - Class III
      - Maps
        - Lists, orders, pamplets, 1945 (Box 19, Folder 139)
      - Miscellaneous: correspondence, petty cash, 1945-1946 (Box 19, Folder 140)
      - Officers: Questionnairs for Staff Officers School for Asiatic Studies and Correspondence
        - A-W, 1946-1962 (Box 20, Folder 141-143)
        - Status and Academic Background and Rating Report: Class I, II, III, IV, V, 1946 (Box 20, Folder 144)
      - Orientation material, 1946 (Box 20, Folder 145)
      - Personnel, 1945 (Box 20, Folder 146)
      - Potsdamn Declaration, 1945 (Box 20, Folder 147)
      - Publicity, 1945 (Box 20, Folder 148)
      - Quarterly papers: list of topics, 1945-1946 (Box 20, Folder 149)
      - Ratings of lectures, 1946 (Box 20, Folder 150)
      - Reading assignments 1st to 14th week, 1946 (Box 20, Folder 150a)
      - Requisitions, 1945-1946 (Box 20, Folder 151-153)
      - Roster, 1945-1946 (Box 20, Folder 154)
      - Rowe, David (Curriculum Director) correspondence and memoranda to him from his office during summer, 1946 (Box 20, Folder 155)
      - St. Anthony Hall: room plan, 1946 (Box 20, Folder 156)
      - Schedule of Lectures, 1946 (Box 20, Folder 157)
      - Schedules, summary of, 1946 (Box 20, Folder 158)
      - Soviet Union: charts, 1945-1946 (Box 20, Folder 159)
      - Temporary employees: employment vouchers, 1945-1946 (Box 20, Folder 160)
      - Travel Expense Reports, 1945-1947 (Box 20, Folder 161)
      - War Department Reports (restricted), 1945 (Box 20, Folder 162)
  - Printed Material
    - "American Policy toward China" by David N. Rowe, 1948 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Burmese alphabet and writings, undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Chinese Historical Library, A Select, undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - "Collective Security in the Pacific: An American View" by David N. Rowe, 1944 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - "Communist China Looks at the United States" by Richard L. Walker, 1951 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Constitution of the Mongol Peoples Republic, 1940 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Foreign Area Studies: A Proposed Outline for an Integration Seminar, undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - "How to Misunderstand China" by Richard L. Walker, 1951 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Japanese constitution, 1946 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Literature from Communist China by Richard L. Walker, 1951 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Marshall's (General) statement on strife in China, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - "Outline Sketch of Chinese History" by David N. Rowe, undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Periodicals on the Far East: list, undated (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Potsdam Declaration, 1945 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Russian 25, 1949 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - "Sound and Symbol in Chinese" by Bernard Karlgren, undated (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Training of civil and military officials for special service in China and Japan: memoranda by David N. Rowe, undated (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Translations of Chinese periodicals, 1945 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Civilian Affairs Training School, printed materials on the Pacific theater in World War II, circa 1941-1961; Accession 19ND-A-171
  The materials are open for research.
  - Address at Public Safety Officer's School, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Annex "L" to Operation Plan No. 1-44 Guam, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Army Service Forces Office of Commanding General Memoranda for Directors and Associate Directors, CATS, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda for Directors and Associate Directors, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Check Lists for Civilian Supply Officers, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - CATS - Audit Instruction No. 1 SHAEF, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Civil Affairs Training Schools
    - Instructional Bulletin No. 1, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Informational Bulletin No. 4, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Informational Bulletin No. 5, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Information Bulletin No. 6, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Information Bulletin No. 7, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Information Bulletin No. 8, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Information Bulletin No. 9, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - CATS - Medical Sanitary and Veterinary Supplies for the Far East, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - CATS - Procedure for Delousing with Powder, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Civilian Defense, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Civilian Supplies for Military Govement (Foreign Economic Administration), 1944 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Coments on the Medical Situation in Japan, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Duties and Responsibilities of AAV, Echelon Supply and Economics Bkanch, G-5 Division, Supreme Headquarters AEF, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Report of Finance Division, USGCC, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Finance Policies and Procedures for Philippine Civil Affairs Units, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Fire Departmnt Operational Practices in Japan, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Fire Protection in the Theatre of Operations, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - General Climatic Information Guides - Japan, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Instructional Notes on Philippine Civil Affairs, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Interdepartmental Committee for the Acquisition of Foreign Publications
    - Abstracts, 1941-1945 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Subject Indices, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Island Commander and Air Commander Tarawa - General Order No. 5, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Maps - Japan, China, 1943-1947 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Miscellaneous Philippines - Japan, 1944-1945 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Notes on Censorship and Security, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Notes on Saipan, Tinian, Guam, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Observations on Military Government Operations, Pacific Areas, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Outline for Civil Affairs/Military Government Public Health Technical Operations, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Public Health Instructions for Military Government Officers, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Report of Visit to Sicily by Colonel H.L. White and Lt. Colonel S.E.H. Dow, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Sample Mailings for ROTC and NROTC, 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Security Plan - Civilians, V Corps, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Standing Operating Procedure #27 Civil Administration and Relief of the Philipines, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Table of Allowances, Civil Affairs Unit, USAFFE, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Civilian Affairs Training School, printed reports, circa 1943-1945; Accession 19ND-A-172
  - Army Service Forces to CATS: Memoranda, 1944 December - 1945 August
    - Instructional checks for civilian supply officers, 1944 December 20 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - List of Japanese Clubs, Societies, Associations, 1944 December 27 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Organization of Allied Commission in Italy, 1945 February 6 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Supreme Headquarters Allied Expeditionary Force reports, 1945 February 10 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Use of silver coins as occupational currency, 1945 February 23 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Supreme Headquarters Allied Expeditionary Force Administrative Memorandum #33, 1945 March 13 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Visit to Gila River Relocation Center, 1945 March 22 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Use of silver coins as occupational currency, 1945 April 12 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Outline of the organization and activities of Japanese Red Cross, 1945 April 26 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Notes on Commercial Aviation in Japan, 1945 May 22 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Troop purchases in Germany, 1945 May 24 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Information bulletin #10, Japan, 1945 May 25 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Notes and Comments on Military Courts, 1945 June 7 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Activities of Army Military Government (A.M.G.) in European Theatre, 1945 June 27 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - "The Aspect of War and the Japanese Political Situation", 1945 June 27 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - "The Nature of Japanese Totalitarianinsm", 1945 July 2 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Report from Austria, 1945 July 10 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Removal of Nazis and Militarists, 1945 July 26 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Mining Industry in Manchuria and Mongolia, 1945 August 2 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Civilian Affairs Training Schools, 1944 December - 1945 Jun, undated
    - University of Chicago: lectures and papers [see also box 4, folder 110], 1944 December - 1945 Apr, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Northwestern University: class syllabi, 1945 May (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - University of Michigan: class syllabi, 1945 April (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Stanford University: abstracts and surveys, 1945, n,d. (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Yale University: lectures and abstracts, 1944 September - 1945 Jun, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Unidentified School, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Interdepartmental Committee for the Acquisition of Foreign Publications
    - Subject Index to Foreign Publications 1944 Nov - 1945 Mar
      - Japan
        - 1944 Nov 28 (Box 2, Folder 26)
        - 1945 Jan 23 (Box 2, Folder 27)
        - 1945 Feb 1, 2 (Box 2, Folder 28)
        - 1945 Apr 2, 6 (Box 2, Folder 29)
        - 1945 May 5, 10 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Hungary, 1945 May 12 (Box 2, Folder 31)
      - Japan
        - 1945 May 15, 24 (Box 2, Folder 32)
        - 1945 Jun 2, 14 (Box 2, Folder 33)
        - 1945 Jun 15, 29 (Box 2, Folder 34)
        - 1945 Ju1 12, 13, 14 (Box 2, Folder 35)
      - Japan: Administrative organization, Laws, Degrees and Regulations. References from The Subject Index, 1944 November 28 (Box 2, Folder 36)
      - Supplement to Subject Index to Foreign Publications, Translation of Tables of Contents of Japanese Publications #10, #11, 1945 March 23, 25 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Abstracts on European and Far Eastern Personalities, 1945 February-July
      - Supplement, 1945 February 7 (Box 2, Folder 38)
      - Supplement, 1945 March 7, 14, 28 (Box 2, Folder 39)
      - Personalities, 1945 May 2, 10, 25, 30, 31 (Box 2, Folder 40)
      - Personalities, 1945 June 6, 13, 20, 27, 28 (Box 2, Folder 41)
      - Personalities, 1945 July 4 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Foreign Publications Abstracts: Japan, 1943-45
      - Agriculture
        - including Government Control (Box 2, Folder 43)
        - Vegetables (Box 2, Folder 44)
        - Field Crops (including fodder) (Box 2, Folder 45)
      - Armed Forces (including Army, Navy, and Airforce) (Box 2, Folder 46)
      - Art, Science, Technology (Box 2, Folder 47)
      - Civil Defense (including Evacuations, Special Measures, Aerial Defense, Air Raids, Emergency Rationing). Tokyo (Box 2, Folder 48)
      - Communications
        - Includes Transportation (Box 2, Folder 49)
        - Government Control (Box 2, Folder 50)
        - Water (including Merchant Marine) (Box 2, Folder 51)
        - Wireless (Box 2, Folder 52)
      - Control Associations #2763 - #6528 (Box 2, Folder 53)
      - Control Associations #6938 - #14050 (Box 2, Folder 54)
      - Economics - Finance
        - #6515, #19072 (Box 2, Folder 55)
        - #11007 - #13446 (Box 2, Folder 56)
        - Including Insurance, Commerce, Surveys (Box 2, Folder 57)
        - Including Banks and Stock Exchange (Box 2, Folder 58)
        - Including Monatary Policies and Control, Government Control (Box 3, Folder 59)
        - National Budget (Box 3, Folder 60)
        - Taxation (Box 3, Folder 61)
        - Including Subsidies and Loans, Government Loans, Forced Savings, Business Loans (Box 3, Folder 62)
        - Price Control (Box 3, Folder 63)
        - Price Movements (Box 3, Folder 64)
      - Education (Box 3, Folder 65)
      - Food (Box 3, Folder 66)
      - Food, Government Control (Box 3, Folder 67)
      - Communication, Land (including Local Railroads, Roads and Trails, Telephone, Postal, Telegraph) (Box 3, Folder 68)
      - Government, Central (including Organization, Local Government, Foreign Relations) (Box 3, Folder 69)
      - Industry
        - Information re (Box 3, Folder 70)
        - Aircraft (Box 3, Folder 71)
        - Arms and Armament (Box 3, Folder 72)
        - Chemical (Box 3, Folder 73)
        - Fishing (Box 3, Folder 74)
        - Fuel (Box 3, Folder 75)
        - General file (Box 3, Folder 76)
        - Government Contro1 (Box 3, Folder 77)
        - Heavy Industry (Box 3, Folder 78)
        - Mining (including metals) (Box 3, Folder 79)
        - Paper (including Lumbering and Milling, Printing and Publishing) (Box 3, Folder 80)
        - Production (including Raw Materials) (Box 3, Folder 81)
        - Railroads (Box 3, Folder 82)
        - Textile (including silk) (Box 3, Folder 83)
      - Manpower
        - Including Civilian Recruitment and Training, Shortages (Box 3, Folder 84)
        - Labor (female) (Box 3, Folder 85)
        - Labor (including Foreign Government Control, Recruitment and Training, Wages and Welfare) (Box 3, Folder 86)
        - Mobilization (Box 3, Folder 87)
        - Personalities: Army, Counsulor and Diplomatic Service, Communications, Finance, Government, Imperial Family, Industry, Medicine, Navy, Social Worker, Women leaders (Box 3, Folder 88)
        - Population (Box 3, Folder 89)
        - Public Opinion: Views and Interpretations (including Prizes and Awards, Group Attitudes) (Box 3, Folder 90)
      - Rationing
        - Daily necessities (Box 3, Folder 91)
        - Food (including Fish, Rice, Sugar) (Box 3, Folder 92)
        - General (including clothing, matches, paper, and fuel) (Box 3, Folder 93)
      - Social Conditions (including Women, Public welfare) (Box 3, Folder 94)
      - Shipbuilding (shipping) (Box 3, Folder 95)
      - China (includes Nationalist and Communist Governments) (Box 4, Folder 96)
      - China (occupied) (Box 4, Folder 97)
      - Czechoslavakla, Hungary, USSR, Yugoslavla (Box 4, Folder 98)
      - Formosa (Box 4, Folder 99)
      - Korea (Box 4, Folder 100)
      - Denmark, Germany, Norway (Box 4, Folder 101)
      - Manchuria (Box 4, Folder 102)
      - Southeast Asia (including Greater East Asia, Hong Kong, Malaya, French Indo-China and Kwangchowan) (Box 4, Folder 103)
    - Miscellaneous Printed Material and Reports (Japan, Germany), 1944 March - 1945, undated
      - The American Magazine, "G-Men in Khaki", 1945 January (Box 4, Folder 104)
      - Army Map Service, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 105)
      - Civil Affairs, 1944 June 26 - 1945 April 18 (Box 4, Folder 106)
      - J. B. Powell "After We've Occupied Japan", 1944 November (Box 4, Folder 107)
      - Army Service Forces Manual, Civil Affairs Handbook, Japan, Section 15, Education, 1944 June 23 (Box 4, Folder 108)
      - Collapse of the Tojo Cabinet, undated (Box 4, Folder 109)
      - Japan: Emergency Relief during the earthquake of 1923, 1944 October 11 (Box 4, Folder 110)
      - Japan's Local Administrative Districts, undated (Box 4, Folder 111)
      - Wartime Changes in Japan, undated (Box 4, Folder 112)
      - Lt. Col. William A, Breswer, "Passive Air Defense Measures in connection with Military Operation" lecture, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 113)
      - Bruce E, Clarke, The Relationship of Intelligence and liason to Military Government, undated (Box 4, Folder 114)
      - Bureau of Labor Statistics Labor Conditions in China, 1944 August 2 (Box 4, Folder 115)
      - Department of Agriculture, Division of Forest Economics - Forest Service, Japan: Forest Resources, Forest Products, Forest Policy, 1945 May (Box 4, Folder 116)
      - Federal Communications Commission, Foreign Broadcast Intelligence Service, Who's Who in Japan, 1945 February 23 - 1945 May 25 (Box 4, Folder 117)
      - Foreign Economic Advisory Administration Special Areas Branch Economic Who's Who in Japan, 1944 January (Box 4, Folder 118)
      - Government Printing Office, Hugh Berton, The Administration and Structure of Japanese Government, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 119)
      - JICA China Branch Reports, 1945 April 30 (Box 4, Folder 120)
      - Navy Department
        - Military Government Section, 1944 December - 1945 May (Box 4, Folder 121)
        - Military Government Section, Credit Cooperatives and Mutual Loan Societies in Japan, 1945 February 15 (Box 4, Folder 122)
        - Hospitals (Navy), undated (Box 4, Folder 123)
      - Office of Strategic Services
        - Local Government in Japan, 1944 August 1 (Box 4, Folder 124)
        - Japanese Films: A Phase of Psychological Warfare, 1944 March 30 (Box 4, Folder 125)
        - SPMDW Japan: Descriptive Summary of Ground Water Resources, undated (Box 4, Folder 126)
        - Supreme Headquarters Allied Expeditionary Force (SHAEF), 1944 July - 1945 Jan, undated (Box 4, Folder 127 - 128)
        - (Unidentified magazine) Lt. Robert B. Sheeks, "Civilians on Saipan" gallery proofs, undated (Box 4, Folder 129)
        - Unidentified reports, undated (Box 4, Folder 130)
        - Newspaper clipping (New York Times), 1945 April 30 (Box 4)
- Indonesian language lessons, circa 1943; Accession 1988-A-060
  - Indonesian language teaching aids, circa 1943
    - Lessons 1-20 (Box 1, Folder 1-5)
- Army Specialized Training Program student transcripts, 1943-1945; Accession 2005-A-117
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2026
  - Abbott, George Robert (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Abler, Morton (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Acosta, Eduardo Augusts (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Adams, Jimmy Blackburn (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Adler, Murray Laurence (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Aed, Sammie Tofe (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Agin, John Robert (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Agnew, Leonard James (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Agnew, Royce Emmonds (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Agree, Jack (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Agronick, Joseph Paul (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Aikens, Keith Robert (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Ainsworth, Walland Vance (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Aldrich, Earl Everett (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Alexander, Charles John (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Alexopoulos James (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Aley, Maxwell Parkhurst (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Allen, Frederick Goodwin (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Allen, Thomas Heber (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Alper, Harold (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Althoff, Clifford Floyd (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Amen, Elwood Everett (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Anderson, Edgar B (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Anderson, James Walden (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Anderson, Paul Herbert (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Anderson, Samuel George (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Andrews, Joseph William III (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Anex, George Charl (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Anthony, Richard Wayne (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Apple, Edward Joseph Jr (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Applebaum, Harold (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Arendt, Herbert John (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Arias, Joseph Manuel (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Armstrong, Robert Weeks Jr (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Arndt, Frederick Harold (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Arner, Douglas Gene (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Arrowsmith Noel Stryker (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Arthur, Charles Newman (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Arvin, Robert Hawkins (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Aschoff, Walter William (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Atchison, Liston Sherwood Jr (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Atherton, Harry Randell (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Aub, Richard (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Aubrey, George Leslie (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Aubuchon, Andre' Roland (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Axthelm, Glen Eldon (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Ayerst, Robert Irvin (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Babel, William Thornton (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Babich, John (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Bachelder, Franklin Pennell (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Bachman, Jonathan Davis (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Bail, Donald William (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Bailey, Warren Everson (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Baimes, John (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Baird, John William (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Baker, Cary Forney Jr (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Baker, Douglas Haden (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Baker, Richard James Jr (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Bakken, Virgil Burnell (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Bakunas, Alphonse Andrew (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Baley, Joseph Emil (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Ball, Simon (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Ballard, Frank (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Barbash, Abraham Jack (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Barnard, Rober Conant (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Barnett, Thomas Clement (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Barone, John Anthony (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Barrack, Shyleur (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Barrio, Raymond Saturnino (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Bass, Thomas Hutcheson (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Bastianelli John James (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Battaglia, Bernard Francis (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Bauder, Howard LaVerne (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Bauer, Charles Edward (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Bauer, Richard James (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Bayless, Bert Oscar (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Beach, Brewster Yale (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Bean, Allen Crosby (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Beck, Warren Edwin (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Becker, Abraham Samuel (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Beckman, Robert Clarence (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Beeks, John Charles (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Behrman, Robert Abner (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Bekler, Konrad (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Bell, James Byran (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Bell, james Malone Jr (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Bender, Bernard (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Bender, Serge Rene' (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Bender, Walter Lee (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Beninson, Leonard (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Bennett, Harvey S (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Bennett, Hite, Jr (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Berg, Irving (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Berger, Milton Albert (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Bergin, Thomas Francis (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Bergofsky, Irvin Jack (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Berman, Frank Wolfgang (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Bernkopf, Michael (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Bernkopf, Michael (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Bernstein, Louis Robert (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Berro, Morris (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Berry, Moses (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Bertocchi, Robert Paul Jr (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - Beyer, Joseph Patrick (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Bezark, Armand Irwin (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - Bialstock, Morton (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - Bianco, Americo John (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - Biddle, Robert Guy (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - Bidne, Howard Orline (Box 1, Folder 109)
  - Bilodeau, Laurent Charles (Box 1, Folder 110)
  - Bingham, Francis Stafford (Box 1, Folder 111)
  - Bird, Derwin Edward (Box 1, Folder 112)
  - Black, James Irving (Box 1, Folder 113)
  - Blackwell, David Jefferson (Box 1, Folder 114)
  - Bladek, Frank Albert (Box 1, Folder 115)
  - Blahunka, John Stephen (Box 1, Folder 116)
  - Blakeslee, Wallace Peckham (Box 1, Folder 117)
  - Blakey, Robert Turner (Box 1, Folder 118)
  - Blanke, Darwin August (Box 1, Folder 119)
  - Blazok, Leo Charles (Box 1, Folder 120)
  - Bliss, Benjamin Borden (Box 1, Folder 121)
  - Block, Haskell Mayer (Box 1, Folder 122)
  - Blodgett, Theron Herbert (Box 1, Folder 123)
  - Bodenheim, Herbert (Box 1, Folder 124)
  - Bodian, Alfred (Box 1, Folder 125)
  - Boewe, Verne Carl (Box 1, Folder 126)
  - Bohacek, Stuart John (Box 1, Folder 127)
  - Bohager, Bernard Carl (Box 1, Folder 128)
  - Bokrosh, Joseph (Box 1, Folder 129)
  - Boldt, William O'Brien (Box 1, Folder 130)
  - Bolson, Robert James Jr (Box 1, Folder 131)
  - Bolter, Arthur (Box 1, Folder 132)
  - Bonchek, Meyer R (Box 1, Folder 133)
  - Bonhaus, Donald Lawrence (Box 1, Folder 134)
  - Bonus, Roman Aseo (Box 1, Folder 135)
  - Born, Henry Wilbur (Box 1, Folder 136)
  - Boroff, David (Box 1, Folder 137)
  - Bos, William Albert (Box 1, Folder 138)
  - Bosse, Martin Lenzi (Box 1, Folder 139)
  - Bostic, James Isham (Box 1, Folder 140)
  - Bourgeois, Aldric Roland (Box 1, Folder 141)
  - Bourgeois, Louis Clarence III (Box 1, Folder 142)
  - Bowman, B E (Box 1, Folder 143)
  - Boyko, Fred Sergey (Box 1, Folder 144)
  - Bracco, Armando Alfonso (Box 1, Folder 145)
  - Bradley, Forrest Wayne (Box 1, Folder 146)
  - Brandes, Ralph Harry (Box 1, Folder 147)
  - Brandstater Max (Box 1, Folder 148)
  - Brandt, Gerhard Max (Box 1, Folder 149)
  - Branstrom, Donald Frederick (Box 1, Folder 150)
  - Brant, John Myers (Box 1, Folder 151)
  - Braverman, Albert (Box 1, Folder 152)
  - Braverman, Charles (Box 1, Folder 153)